Hello Hello friends if you
want to know more about the new updates of To Balance,
about their problems, new updates of Twenty20
then watch this video till the end.
In the alarm key, Tubelight has launched a new update called
Insurance Juice, so you can
also take out insurance through the Tubelight application.
What type of insurance will you
get in this video, I am going to tell you
if you have not downloaded this application yet
then you will
get a link inside the description, you can download WhatsApp
and download the Desi app, after downloading
you will
get ₹10 cash loot on top of To Balance for August and September so friends
what you have to do here is
open Tubelight, you have installed it,
downloaded it, then an
interface will open in front of you like this, secondly here you can see that
many services have been provided here,
here you can get cash loan, level
loan, gift card, mobile shop, incident hour,
gold shop, club, start start pan
and here it provides all these services
Problem and you can click here
or under the Star Channel subscribe button
you
can download the video WhatsApp, here I have
made a video, so that link can also be found inside the button
and I have made a gift video, you
can also see that button,
so friends, here in this video
I am going to tell you about insurance, how to
get insurance, so friends please
on insurance, here you will get
life insurance, personal accident
insurance, you will get high interest from the bank,
this life insurance of the hospital and if
you already have a two wheeler, then you can
take out its benefit, so friends, here you have to get it done and take care of your life and depend on it, then
you
can also take out life insurance here, it will cost you ₹3 per
month, now how will you go to the hospital,
you will have to pay ₹150 for that, today I am telling you here this ₹50, that means if you want to take out insurance, then you will have to pay
150 for that and
whatever amount is there in the hospital here, if
you have any disease or anything, then you will get the
related service here  If you
click on life insurance, you
can see that you have to pay a third fee.
If you pay,
you will get a benefit of Rs 1 lakh.
Tubelight is
not going to give you Rs 1 lakh, but
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
Company is going to give it to you. Friends, it has done this
through two balances. You only have to make card
payments. If you pay it, you will get
some benefit from it, that is, you will
get a date.
After this, see how about the hospital here.
Here we have 150, that is, you have to
pay 150 for this year. You will take the
hospital, this will give you seven days. So
here, I mean, I will tell you all that
see here, how much does it mean if
you have A below you, then you will
not have to pay anything above N, so
you can see here
[music]
and listen,
and listen, you
can read all these things. Now, in
this way, you can take out an insurance of Rs 50 here.
Hospital is important
strength and after that, dengue insurance. So, this is a
very interesting insurance, you  If you see,
this is of ICICI Lombard, here you
can see that you have to pay only for
25-21 years, how much money will you get if it is an animal,
then see here if there is any animal attack or you face
any problem due to dengue attack,
so that in 1 lakh rupees, there is
a special chapter born in this
related hospitalization benefit,
here you can see that
you will get related hospitalization benefit, that is, if
you have hospitalization benefit, then
you get this benefit up to ₹ 5000,
we get 5,000 more, this means water which is
more, so this company
provides you money, withdrawal benefit from malaria,
benefit
is hospitalization benefit, there is a problem of five youth
and a pond of 5,000 pistachios is
required, so friends, here this
company will provide us money,
so friends, in this way, here you will get this
insurance from Friday, for more information
I am yours  For this, in my studio I am going to tell
you about the complete insurance, that is,
if someone extracts juice from a person, then its chanting
becomes obscene, till then you have to
wait friends, after this see
personal accident, so here you will
see, here it is two lakhs, but I have applied total
disability, see here you will get
₹5 only rs.5, so you have to pay only water
pistachio, you can take out insurance, so
see here for mantra you have to pay more for
one year, here it is ₹50, after this
here you will see the improvements,
friends, here you
can select any plan like this,
you can select obscene wash at any time, so in
this way it has
brought an update on this problem, so
how did you like it, that is, if you liked the video then
like it and if you are new to this channel
then subscribe to the channel along with the
qualification of increasing the bell icon so that you can
get balance related updates in this way friends, see you
in the next video, till then
why have we gone to Vande Mataram